Finding Aid for William Albright Papers 1962-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Recordings
  - Other Composers/Performers
    - Curran, Alvin, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Currier, N., 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Currier, Sebastian, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Curtis-Smith, C
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 77)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Daugherty, Michael
      - [version 1], 2 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
        (taped with Colgrass)
    - Danforth, Frances, 2 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Davidovsky, Mario, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Davidson, Matthew, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      (taped with Brass Knuckles)
    - Davies, Maxwell, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Davies, P.M., 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Decker, Pamela, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Denisov, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Deutsch, Daniel, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Diemer, Emma Lou, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Dollarhide, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Druckman, J
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Dun Tan, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Durkee, Arthur, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Dzubay, David
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
        (taped with Kurek)
    - Eberhard, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Eberhard, Dennis, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Eidschun, Robert, 2 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Engleskyts, [?], 2 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Estonian/Latvian, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Faber, Nan, 2 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Farwell, Arthur, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
      (taped with Zonn)
    - Fejko, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Felber, Jill, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Felciano, Richard, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - Ferguson, J., 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Fields, Matthew), 3 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Finney, Ross Lee
      - [version 1], 3 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
      - [versions 3-4], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - First Unitarian Universalist Church of Ann Arbor (special music), 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - The Fischer Duo, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Foley, David F., 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - Fortner, Jack
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
        (taped with Cacioppo)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
        (taped under U-M Orchestra)
    - Friedman, Harry, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Fry, James, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Garant, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Garrett, George, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Garrop, Stacy, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Gentile, Ada], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      (taped with Benjamin)
    - George, Ron, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Goble, Dan, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Godfrey, Daniel S.), 6 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Gompper, David, 5 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Gottschalk, Arthur, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Grabowsky, Paul, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Grisey, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - Grop, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      (taped with Buchman)
    - Gross, Robert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Gruber, H.K., 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Gryc, Stephen, 3 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Hacha, Chris, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Halffter (?), Cristobal, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Halle, John, 2 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Hamel, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hamel, Keith, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hand, Ferderic, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hanway, Judith, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Harbison, [?] (Box 66)
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
        (taped with Scelsi)
    - Harlem Spiritual Ensemble, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hause, Evan, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hayes, Jeff, 3 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Henze, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Herrsen, Jan, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hershey, Sharon
      - [version 1], 3 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
        (taped with Gompper)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
      - [versions 5-6], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Hill, Augustus O., 2 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hodkinson, Sydney
      - [version 1], 6 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 80)
      - [version 3], 4 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
        (taped with Curtis-Smith)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
        (taped with Albright's Beulahland Rag)
    - Hogan, Leslie, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hollthamp (?), [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Howrani, W., 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Hurley, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Iannaccone, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      (taped with Phipps)
    - Ince, Kamran), 6 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Jaffe, Stephen, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Jankowski, Loretta, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      (taped with Albright's Foils)
    - Jenni, D. Maring, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Jennings, Richard, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Johnson, A. Paul, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Johnson, Pete, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Joyce, Donald), 3 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kapae, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      (taped with Halffter)
    - Karpman, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kennedy, John M., 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kernis, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kertag (or Kurtag), G.
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
        (taped with Herrsen)
    - Kilstofte, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kirschenmann, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kirshner, Andy, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Knussen, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Koblitz, David, 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Kohl, Hannah, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kolb, Barbara
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
        (taped with J. Adams)
    - Komorous, Rudolf, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      (taped with Steva)
    - Kraft, William, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kramer, Timothy, 3 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Krumm, P., 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kurek, Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kurek, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Kurtz, Eugene
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Larsen, Libby
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
        (taped with Foley)
    - Lenciko, Terry, 1 audiocassettes (Box 72)
      (taped with Mather)
    - Lerdahl, F. (Box 66)
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Levin, Rami, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Levin, Todd
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Levy, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Lifchitz, Max, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      (taped with Morris)
    - Liptak, David, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Lombard, Jeannette, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - London, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Lorenz, Christian, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Luedeke, Raymond, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Lulloff (?), Joe, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Lutoslawski, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - McCabe, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - McShann, Jay, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Machover, Todd
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Malone, Don, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Marshall, Cheryl, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Martino, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Maslanka, David, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Mather, Bruce
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Matthews, William, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Messiaen, Olivier
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Milburn, Ellsworth, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Miles, Thomas, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Moore, Lisa, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Moravec, Paul, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Morris, Joan, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Morris, Robert
      - [version 1], 3 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version-3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
      - [version 5], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 80)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
        (taped with L. Rush)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Morrison, John, 3 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Mott, David, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Monahan, Gordon, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Mongomery, Jim, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Nancarrow, Conlon
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
        (taped with Krumm)
    - Neil, William, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Neilson, D., 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Nelson, Larry, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Newby, Stephen Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Newcomb, Robert, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Nez, Ketty, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Nordheim, Arna
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Novak, Bob, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Olivera, Hector, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - O'Neill, M., 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Pacifica 5, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Palmer, Glenn, 2 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Pann, Carter, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Pape, Gerard, 3 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Part, Arvo, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Partlow, Mary, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Paulsson, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Peck, Russell
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Pehrson, Joseph, 1 audiocassettes (Box 81)
    - Penn, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 67)
    - Peterson, H., 1 audiocassettes (Box 73)
    - Peterson, J., 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Phan, P.Q.), 7 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Phipps, Karen), 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Pichet, Jean
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Paulus, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      (taped with Larsen)
    - Place, David, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Plain, Gerald
      - [versions 1-4], 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Poupart, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Powell, Mel, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Pratt, M., 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Radzynski, Jan
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
        (taped with Andriessen)
    - Rea, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Reese, Luke W., 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Reich, Scott, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Reich, Steve, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Riley, Terry, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Roberts, David Thomas, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rochberg, George, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Rodgers [L.?]
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Ronen, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rose, Matt, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Ross, [?]
      - [version 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rosza, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Roumain, Daniel, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rouse, Chris, 2 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rouse, Steve
      - [versions 1-11], 11 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      - [version 12], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 3 1/4" (Box 73)
    - Ruders, Poul, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
      (taped with Abramsen)
    - Runchak, Volodymyr, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rush, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Rush, Loren, 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Rush, Stephen, 2 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rutkowski, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Rzowski, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Saariaho, Kaija, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Sanabria, Peter, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Sandler, Felicia, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Santos, Erik, 2 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Sanwell, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Scelsi, G.), 3 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - Schaefer, R. Murray
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
        (taped with Cherney)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Schell, Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Schiff, David, 2 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Schmitke, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Schober, David, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Schramm, Betsy L., 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Schwantner, Joseph
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 81)
    - Schwartz, Elliott
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Schwertsik, K., 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Seely, Bob, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 77)
    - Sewell, Jess, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Shadrin, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Shapey, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Shen, Hsu-Yun, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Shrude, Marilyn, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Siegel, Eric, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Sierra, Roberto
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
        (taped with Amlin)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
        (taped with N. Currier)
    - Sin, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Singer, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Sloan, Donald, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Smalley, Roger, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Smith, Tim, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Sosin, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Steva, Ronald, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Stiller, Andrew, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Stoltzman, Richard, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
      (taped with Hand)
    - Strong, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Subotnik, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
      (taped with Dzubay)
    - Suslin, Victor, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Thoresen, Lasse, 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Thorne, [?], 2 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Tichelli, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Timpson, [?], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 68)
    - Tjheknavaraian [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Torke, Michael, 2 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Underhill, Owen, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
    - University of Michigan Orchestra 1967, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Ung, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Van Buren, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Vayo, David, 3 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Vinao, Alejandro, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
    - Vivier, Claude, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Warner, Scott, 2 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Wells, Thomas, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Whitaker, Howard, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - White, B.A., 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Willey, James, 2 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Wilson, Don, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      (taped with Ashley)
    - Wilson, George Balch (Box 81)
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Winchester, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Winges, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Winkler, Peter, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
    - Winsor, Phil (Box 68)
      - [versions 1-5], 5 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      - Woolf, Randall, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Worley, Daniel, 5 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - You, Than, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Youtz, Gregory), 3 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Zajonc, Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
    - Zimmerman, Berdt A., 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
    - Zonn, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 73)
    - Zorn, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
- Videocassettes
  One videocassette is included in the series Videocassettes. "Ragtime Christmas Bash" is a recording of this 1988 concert at the First Unitarian Universalist Church of Ann Arbor.
  - "Ragtime Christmas Bash," 1988 (Box 77)
- Posters
  The final series is Posters. Included are approximately 110 posters from various musical events.
  - Posters from various musical events 1964-1998 (Box 82)